Now, let's go ahead and check out a quick demo of IMer rules and I am permissions and policies.
So, there's a possibility that it can be tested in the exam.
And what I want to show you is, what is the kind of IMer rule permissions and policies?
We need to attach to different AWS services so that they can access Amazon bedrock.
And in this use case, what I'm going to show you is, so we'll have a user,
so we'll pass a prompt or a user input where this AWS EPA gateway, which will go as an event
to this lambda function. And then this lambda function is going to query the Amazon bedrock
and the underlying foundation model, which is go here in this use case.
So, I will show you what is the right IM role and policy we need to attach to this lambda
function so that it can access the Amazon bedrock service. So, I'm going to show you only this portion
of the demo lambda function and how it will invoke the Amazon bedrock service.
So, I'm on the AWS console now and for the purpose of this demo,
I've already written a lambda function that is going to query Amazon bedrock service
and specifically this coherent command light model. Now, what I have done is, if I just go to
configuration and you can see attached a random role called a CDK role, which does not have the
permission to access the Amazon bedrock service. So, if I just go back to this code
and I will just show you the test event. So, here I have the test event and we say
where is London and now, once I send this query to the Amazon bedrock service, it should be able
to give me an answer if it has the right permission. Let me just go back to the code and let me
just try it out. Let me just click on test and you can see it is given an error, access denied
exception when calling invoke model operation. So, which means it does not have the right, I am
policy because it cannot invoke the model. Now, can do this, I can go back to the I am service.
So, I am on the I am identity service. Now, if I just go to these roles, click on the role
and I can just say create a role. Now, you can see it is asking me which is the AWS service
to which you want to attach this role. So, is it an AWS service, is it an AWS account,
web identity, custom trust policy and so on. So, what I will do is here is I will select the
service. So, in our case, it is going to be the AWS Lambda function as you can see here. So,
I will click on next. Now, I have to attach a permission policy to this particular Lambda function
and this permission policy is basically which AWS service it needs access to and in our case,
it is going to be Amazon bedrock. So, what I will do is I will just search for bedrock. So,
you can see I have lot created lot of custom policies and if we just filter here. So, it can be
either AWS standard policies so AWS manage or it can be a customer managed. So, I have created
lot of custom I am role but I will just select AWS managed for this use case and you can see here.
So, you have if we can just push it on to the right. So, if Amazon bedrock full access, Amazon
bedrock read only and if I just click on this policy, so you can see I have a JSON file which talks
about what is the kind of permission that this particular policy provides. So, I will just click here
and just click on this Amazon bedrock full access, just click on next and let us give it a name.
Let us say demo I am Udemy. So, then I will just click on create role. So, you can see
role demo I am Udemy has been created. So, if I just go back here and now if I just click on
configuration and here is the role name. So, if I just went edit and if I just scroll down. So,
here you can see existing role. So, I will replace it with what we had created and which is
demo I am Udemy. So, I will just say demo I am Udemy and here is the role. So, I will just click on
save. Okay, now if I just go back to the code and if I just click on test, now it should work because
we have provided the lambda function right I am role to be able to access the Amazon
bedrock service. Now, you can see it is giving me a response let me just increase the size.
Okay, so we can see here now we got a response. London, England is the south eastern region of
UK and if you see what was our question where is London. Okay, so if I just go back to the I am
role for a couple of minutes. So, you can see here we already discussed about user groups,
users, roles and then we also have the policies. And as we discussed a policies and object in AWS
that defines permissions. So, there could be an AWS managed job function like admin, billing,
admin and so on and there could be any AWS managed policies like what we just saw on bedrock,
S3 and so on. And then it could also be customer managed so you can write your own policies.
Okay, so that is pretty much it from this lecture. I hope it was useful. Thank you.